Nand Gondha

DevOps Engineer

- "Nandalay", C-185, Goldencity 3, Junagadh, Gujarat 362001
- in linkedin.com/in/nandgondha

7600345702

- github.com/nandG12
- mand.gondha03@gmail.com

I'm enthusiastic person with 1.5 years experience in Software Development & Cloud Management with ability to Quick learn anything & explore all possible areas. Always found a way on my own & always think out of the box, if the problem comes always first chose quick solution like first aid then give the proper treatment for that problem.



Experience

Jr. DevOps Engineer

Asite Solution - Ahmedabad

- Created & Migrated the Whole new Data Center (KSA DC) of Asite Product.
- Created & Implemented the API of Edge cast (CDN)
- Use of the Jenkins & Other DevOps tools like Serena for the CI-CD pipeline
- Created the WebApp to use daily Deployment & Reducing the repeated task. (Name: Zero Developer Console)
- Created the Python Selenium Scripts for the Daily Testing of basic things(Name: Python---Selennium-Scripts)

Intern

Weybee Solution - Rajkot

- Completed Project the jeweler based system ERP, Based on PHP & MySQL.
- Created the barcode generation code & printing label direct from web.
 (PHP & EZ Programming Language)
- I Have Created the Company Website on Wordpress that is currently in used. (https://www.weybee.com/)
- I Used to handle their Servers on AWS & Digital Ocean Cloud Services. Also Implemented & Used the Different Services Like VestaCP, cPanel & OpenProject for the Server Handling.

Jan 2019 - May 2019

Jan 2020 - Jan 2022

Education

2016 - 2020

Bachelor of Engineering in Information & Technology

- CGPA: 9.34
- Gujarat Technological University | V. V. P Engineering College
- The Best User Award in 2017-18
- CR from 2017 to 2020
- Main Coordinator of Sound Department for Center Level Activities & Main Coordinator for the Departmental Activities & Initiator of the Peer to Peer learning

2014 - 2016

Higher Secondary (HSC)

Percentage: 74.92 %

- Gujarat Secondary and Higher Secondary Education Board
- Shree P. V. Modi High School Rajkot

2013 - 2014

Secondary (HSC)

- Percentage: 84.5 %
- Gujarat Secondary and Higher Secondary Education Board
- Shree N. P. Bhalodia High School Junagadh



WEB Projects

Oct 2020

Motor Vehicle Collisions Data Web Application Data Science

Coursera Project Network

- Language: Python, Streamlit Lib, Numpy, Pandas
- Using the Python & Streamlit Library build the Data Science Web Application to Check the Motor Vehicle Collisions Data in Specific City or Areas using the Charts & Graphs.
- Build a Data Science Web App with Streamlit and Python By Coursera Project Network

April 2020

Zero Developer Console

Asite Solutions

- Language: Python, Flask, Bootstrap, Excel
- It is used for the deployment process for the server just like a jenkins, It is developed for the Automation.

Jan 2020 - Mar 2020

aE - Payment Lyber

Final Year Project | B.E.

- Language: Python, Flask, MySQL, Bootstrap, Selenium
- Lyber is a website which is Automation in E Payment Specially Designed for the Bills payments.
- All Bills can pay using only & only one Transactions. I Have Used PayTM as a thrid party application.
- PPT Link & Code Avilable on the Github.
- nandG12/aE-Payment-Lyber

April 2019

Barcode Generation & Printing label from ERP

Weybee Solutions

- Languages: PHP & EZ Programming Language (By Godex Printer)
- Use the Godex & EZ Programming API to connect with the Web App & print the directly using the one click & implemented barcode in PHP.

Feb 2019

Jan 2018



Research on Machine Translation using NLP | 3rd Rank

• Research in machine translation has comes along way since the idea of using computer to automate the translation process.

Review on Meltdown and Spectre | 1st Rank

• As a review paper writing we review on the topic meltdown & spectre. It is a major problem found in intel hardwares.



Skills

- Presentations skills in Both Simple PowerPoint or Prezi
- Problem Solving by Hacker Rank | 5 Star (Gold level)
- Hacker Rank Different Code Challenges
- Hack the Interview II Global | Rank 1430/4647 | April 2020
- Languages: C, Java, Python, OOP Concepts, SQL, PowerBI, HTML, PHP, JS



Certification Courses

- Build a Data Science Web App With Streamlit & Python | Coursera Project Network
- Using Python to Access Web Data | University of Michigan
- Python Data Structures | University of Michigan



Workshops & Seminar's

Workshop on Mathematics & Applied Data Science by TCET Mumbai Cloud O Sphere'19 Gujcost Sponsored Four days workshop on Cloud

Game with Unity Engine One Day seminar by IET Saurashtra & V. V. P. Engineering College

Android Application Development using Advance GPS Gujcost sponsored

Ethical Hacking Workshop Conducted by Kyrion Technologies on | L. D. College of Engineering, Ahmedabad



Hobby

Football | State Level Winner in Khel Maha Kumbh

Quodophile

Video Games & Strategic Gaming

July 2020 9th Jan to 12th Jan 2019 23th June 2018

> 2nd & 3rd Aug 2018 29th & 30th July 2017





bit.ly/305U4vD